What are you willing to believe?
The Unbelievers is a documentary film directed by Gus Holwerda.
Scientists Richard Dawkins and Lawrence Krauss travel the globe promoting a
scientific worldview and the rational questioning of religious belief.
Self, played by Richard Dawkins.
Self, played by Lawrence Krauss.
Self, played by Ayaan Hirsi Ali.
Self, played by Woody Allen.
Self, played by Cameron Diaz.
Self, played by Ricky Gervais.
The Unbelievers is a 2013 documentary film that follows Richard Dawkins and Lawrence Krauss as they speak publicly around the globe about the importance of science and
reason in the modern world, encouraging others to cast off religious and politically motivated approaches toward what they think to be important current issues.
The film includes short statements by influential people and celebrities such as Stephen Hawking, Ayaan Hirsi
Ali, Sam Harris, Cameron Diaz, Woody Allen, Penn Jillette, Ian McEwan, and David Silverman.
The film received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of atheist, religion, skepticism, atheism, secularism.